Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Currently, your memory pattern
is 1, 3, 5, 4 and 2.
even though it should have been
1 2 3 4 5.
Alan, listen to me.
You have a problem with memorization.
Maybe you had left that room,
but you just couldn't remember?
I don't want to be here anymore.
Please get me out of this place.
But me must plan carefully.
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Can we travel to somewhere
near Rangsit Khlong 12?
I have a friend named Nate.
Are you sure your friend won't send us back to the hospital?
Jealous?
I dunno.
I just don't want anyone else
to matter more to you than I do.
Alan.
Run, hurry!
Found him!
Once upon a time, a man
had a dream he was a floating butterfly.
When the butterfly became weary,
it landed on the branch and fell asleep.
When the butterfly slept,
the man woke up.
When the man fell back asleep again,
the butterfly awakened.
When the butterfly went to sleep,
the man awoke.
The man'd slept,
the butterfly awoke.
Over and over.
Win.
Mister.
Oh, Alan.
Who are you?
Alan.
I'm your dad.
Dad?
Dad.
Alan!
I tried talking to him, but
he hadn't yet spoken much.
He seems different.
Did you do anything?
I increased his
medication dosage.
What medicine, Doctor?
This has been too
much for him already.
It was the same medication,
but at a higher dose.
It was also the best method
for controlling his behavior.
If we hadn't done this,
he wouldn't have calmed
down and cooperated.
And about his hospital escape,
how did he manage to get out?
He might have escaped
through the cemetery.
Why did he escape?
He's never escaped before.
Doctor Nil.
Should we try changing
the treatment method?
Change?
How would you change that?
Isn't what we've been
doing right now our best?
I believe that if
we keep doing this,
he will definitely be treated..
Listen to me, Doc.
I think this method may no
longer be effective with him.
He just forgot who I was today.
I don't want to leave him
here like this anymore.
If this keeps happening,
I'll come take him
home next week.
I...
You asked me to look after him,
but you never had
any faith in me?
I did.
I always trusted you.
But maybe we've
reached the dead-end.
Are you a doctor, huh?
Are you a doctor to state
that this is a dead end?
Are you a doctor with the
authority to judge me like that?
We've been in this
situation for too long.
Don't you ever get tired?
I love him so much, Doctor.
I want him to get better.
But if things like
this continue,
I will not stand it anymore.
You think I didn't love him, Alex?
I love him as much as you do.
And if I were you,
I would never let my loved
ones become like that forever.
Nevertheless,
I'll remain true to what I said.
Sorry Nil,
if I hurted your feelings.
You are free to do as you please.
My duty is over, so if you'd excuse me.
O.
Nil.
What are you doing all alone in here?
I
I need a little change of scenery.
Sometimes being in the same corner
stresses me out.
I've got some things to think about.
Did you
have an argument with Alex in the morning?
Do you think doctors
are allowed to be discouraged?
Do you think we need to be able to handle
every situation?
Do we have to put up with
whatever everyone throws at us?
Doctors are human too.
It's normal for us to be tired.
Right?
What's your opinion on Alan's case?
What about that?
Do you believe we can treat him?
We definitely going to make him better.
Everything all right?
I think I may have to
find someone else
to take over my responsibilities.
Nil.
We have come too far
to give up at this point..
I didn't mean I was
going to stop treating him.
I just feel like I'm not ready.
I'm having trouble managing
several things at once right now
so I may need to take a break before
I'm capable of resuming my duties as a doctor.
Would you look after Alan's case for me?
You can't just throw your work at me like that.
I've thought it through.
What if he doesn't approve of me?
You're closer to him than I am.
You've been with me and Alan
for long enough.
I believe you can do it.
What choices do I have?
Thank you.
I really mean it.
Don't make such a sad face,
you'll get me even more worried.
Alright?
Go for it.
My memory
has started to return
every time I read this journal.
Although I can't remember
exactly what happened that day,
the sensation has never faded.
I have a profound feeling
and I miss him very much.
But I'm starting to have a harder
time recognizing Win's face.
How many days have passed
since Win and I haven't met?
Did something happen to him
after the incident that day?
It's time for your medication, Alan.
Please take the pills.
When you're finished,
please open your mouth.
Is it really necessary to open my mouth?
Just making sure, Alan.
Sure about what?
Alan.
I'm just doing my job.
Who gave the order?
Was it Doctor Nil?
It was my order.
What gives you the authority to order me?
It's my authority as your
case's personal doctor.
My case's personal doctor?
What about Doctor Nil?
At this time,
Doctor Nil has his hands full of cases,
so I took this opportunity to
take over and handle your case in his place.
Personally,
I believe we're quite close.
This wouldn't be a problem for you, is it?
So what?
If I were to have a problem,
would anyone in this place care about me?
Alan.
Try to give it some careful thought.
Have the doctors
really never cared about you?
Weren't the doctors,
all this time,
the ones who were
trying to understand you?
Guess you're right.
I also wanted to let you know that,
as a doctor,
my responsibility is to treat you.
However, treating a
patient until they're cured
is not so simple.
There are numerous
other factors involved.
But do you know
what's the most important?
What is it?
Try to guess.
Medications?
Surgical procedures?
Wrong answers.
Just tell me what
the answer is, Doc.
It's the doctor-patient relationship.
Simply put,
the trust between a doctor and a patient.
Despite how well the treatment is,
if the doctor and the
patient don't trust each other,
that treatment wouldn't work out at all.
We don't need to talk about
whether you'll get better or not.
And the fact that I told
Pete to keep checking
to see if you had taken
all of your medications
not that I didn't trust you,
but I needed to keep records
in accordance with the treatment plan.
Therefore,
should we work together
to help you get better sooner?
If trusting you
means I'll get better sooner,
then let's go for it.
Thank you
for having faith in me.
I promise
that I'll do my best.
Okay.
Alan.
I believe
you'll certainly be well again.
What are your thoughts on the earlier.
That was pretty dramatic.
Dramatic?
I knew you were
acting to earn the patient's trust.
Which nursing school did you graduate from?
Any hospital makes use of this technique.
Hey.
Why do you have to be so serious?
I was just fooling around.
You had a smart mouth when you were in that room.
Guess whose face looks
so stressed right now.
I'm not stressed.
I'm a doctor,
so it's normal for me to appear serious
in order for the patient to trust me.
They called it
the doctor-patient relationship.
Got it?
Brilliant words!
And how about the doctor-nurse relationship?
What do you think?
What are you talking about?
What's the hurry?
What are you doing?
This is a hospital.
Well, a little birdy told me
that you like me.
Who told you that?
I'm going to tell you
that I like you too.
Is it okay to kiss you?
No.
Then,
maybe another time?
How would I know
you're not lying to me?
Guess I'll
have to leave you with this.
I like you, Doctor.
Would you mind if I sit with you?
Sitting alone with your
mind elsewhere like this,
did I wake you up
from the sweet daydream you were having?
Would you like a match?
The dark pieces are yours.
Today is the last day that I'll be here.
I'd like to play a last match with you
on my final day in this place.
If you win,
you can ask me anything.
I'll answer you as much as I can.
Are you interested
in this offer?
Where are you going?
I have to go back home.
So be it.
Today, it seems like
your mind is wandering off.
Perhaps I am going to be the victor.
Do I
look distracted?
Yeah, you look strange.
I don't know.
I can sense that.
So
Win is not coming?
Win?
Alan!
Run, hurry!
I haven't seen
him for a while now.
Oh dear.
I thought the two of you were inseperable.
Did you guys fight or something?
No.
It's kinda strange though.
I didn't feel like I wanted to see him,
nor did I even miss him.
Very strange.
They increased your
medicine dose, haven't they?
Yes.
I see.
That medicine...
what about it?
Take a good look at yourself.
Since the dosage has been increased,
we're calmer than before.
That's because doctors here use medications
to keep the patients under control.
It felt a bit blurry
obedient,
and perfectly happy, right?
But you should ask yourself
if this is actually what you desire.
You seem to have a pretty good grasp of my thoughts.
despite having only known each other for a short time.
I'm just speaking as someone
who has been here for a long time.
and has witnessed lots of things.
Actually, I'm beginning to suspect
that the treatment in this place
haven't improved my condition at all.
There were also the medications
that you said the doctors
increased the dosage of,
which made me look like a nutcase.
Maybe
I was just talking nonsense.
What were you expecting from the patient...
That's not true.
...like me?
If you know something,
you better tell me.
I think that
the two of us
have something in common.
How are we alike?
You and I
have been trying to bridge the gap
between imagination
and reality.
Sometimes,
what we thought were imaginations
or dreams
turned out to be reality.
However, what we believed to be real
got muddled and mixed up
to the point that
we had no idea what was true.
Dreams...
were like hallucinations.
They might have had some kind of truth
trying to communicate with us.
Perhaps it was just a ripped page
from our memory journal.
But, no matter how torn apart it was,
it did contain something
that could be linked to our past.
Checkmate!
Darn it.
Even while hazy,
you still made a comeback.
I was just following my instincts.
Now.
Since I've won,
you have to keep your promise.
Time for you to answer my question
like we agreed.
Who is this man?
You knew him, right?
I really can't
answer that.
You're lying.
You promised
you'd tell me if I won.
This is all I can help you.
You have to find the answers on your own, boss.
That's not true.
You promised me.
You told me we were alike.
If we really are alike
then you must understand how I feel!
Please
I beg you, Si.
Help me!
Please help me!
I've returned something for you under
the table where we first played chess.
No matter what the outcome was today,
I intended to give it back to you anyway.
What is it?
What is it, tell me?
Who is this old man?
Miss Si?
Where are you?
Your family is here to take you home.
No matter how many times
you get haunted,
I want you to trust your own instincts.
Trust your own instincts!
Good luck, chief.
I've returned something for you under
the table where we first played chess.
No matter what the outcome was today,
I intended to give it back to you anyway.
I've compared both of the journals.
The handwriting was certainly mine.
There's no denying that the stories were mine.
This is another notebook in which I wrote,
but I had written it five months ago.
What the heck is this?
Have I been here before?
Today, I had a treatment session
with Doctor Nil
and Doctor O.
Doctor Nil asked me about
the nurse on the other night.
I've never seen that nurse before.
Never had memories of her in my head.
Are you sure
you have never seen this nurse before?
One of the patients
came to greet me in the cafeteria today.
He was pretty cute
and friendly.
He told me his name was Win.
This is not the first time I'm here.
I first met Win five months ago.
Our beginning was the same.
I didn't like him
until we opened up,
spent time together,
fell in love.
What the hell?
My life is a movie that replays back and forth?
Alan?
Alan.
There you are.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
Oh, Pete.
Do you need anything?
Time for your medications.
Alright.
All done.
Alan.
Get plenty of rest
so you can get well soon.
Okay.
Win's room, as I've noted
is either 303
or 305.
I didn't write it down very clearly.
Win.
Alan.
Quick! Get in!
How did you make it here this far?
I miss you so much.
I'm so sorry
I didn't visit you.
Since that day,
I've been scared.
I didn't want to get you in trouble anymore.
Win.
Why...
did you
decide to approach me?
Can you answer me that?
What?
I asked you
why you chose to talk to me
when there were a lot of other people.
I...
I only thought you could be my friend.
I had been alone for a long time,
and I felt lonely.
I wanted to have friends.
Why?
Which time are you referring about, Win?
This notebook
contains our stories.
I just got it
not long ago.
The inside of this notebook
is filled with so many stories
between me and you.
Shall I read
some of them for you?
Which one should I pick first?
Let's read this one.
It was May 5th.
The sun was scorching hot that day.
Win took me for a walk in the garden.
But the sun light was really hot,
so we hid in the shade.
On June 15,
Win was going to take me to the cemetery,
but I was terrified.
So Win told me that
if I no longer felt scared,
he would take me there again
on June 5th.
Win asked me to be his partner.
What's the meaning of all of this?
Hmm?
Would you tell me
what everything in this notebook is all about?
Hmm?
Or
did you scheme up
with those doctors to deceive me?
Huh?
Answer me, Win!
Answer me.
I never wanted to decieve you.
You know,
at this point in my life,
I have lost all my trust in everyone.
The doctors?
Or even with you.
Be honest with me, Win.
How does it feel
to have
to come see my face
everyday
and trick me
every time?
Hmm?
I have reasons
why I had to approach you this way.
What reasons?
Because you have a
memory condition, Alan.
I had to become a stranger in your eyes
again and again.
Why didn't you tell me?
It wasn't easy
that I had to come to you and
tell you we'd known each other,
but you couldn't remember.
I wasn't easy for me at all.
I'd always be the one
missing from your memory,
while in my memory,
you're still in there.
But I've never blamed you, Alan.
Because I loved you so much,
that's why I allowed things to go this way
no matter how many times they'd happen.
If I go back to forgetting things again,
would you come back for me?
Please don't leave me.
Please come back for me.
I promise
no matter how many times it happens again,
I'll always come back for you.
Hey.
There's a place
I'd like to go.
In this notebook
of mine.
I wrote down multiple stories
between myself
and the director's office.
I noted that
I had seen the old man ghost
at the director's office.
I'm sure you know.
There must have been some connection
between me and
that room, for sure.
Would you take me to that room?
If you want me to trust you again,
of course.
Would you, Win?
Is this here?
Why is this the only separated building?
So weird.
This place was probably
where he spent most of his life.
Let's take a look inside.
What do you know about this former director?
He had intended to utilize this land
as a community for psychiatric patients,
but that never happened.
What kind of person was he?
I only know that
he had good intentions
when he built this place.
Because he had also struggled hard
since he had nothing.
From an orphan with no family
to becoming a psychiatrist
who had been acknowledged at that era.
So where is he right now?
Is he dead?
No one knows.
Are you ready?
I'm right here with you,
but in the end...
You're going to have to make
your own decision what to do next.
But if this is the only way
that'll get you the answers,
then there's nothing more to be afraid of.
What?
I saw you were stunned and thought you'd been haunted.
You asshole.
I almost pissed myself.
Shit!
Alan.
Where are you?
Get yourself out here!
Alan.
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
Just answer me!
Remember.
If you can't remember, come back to me.
Return to where?
Where do you want me to go?
Where do I have to return to?
Huh?
Come back to me.
He's not your father.
Who's not my father?
Hey, wait!
Come back!
Did you hear?
Did you hear what he said?
No.
What did he say?
He said my dad
wasn't my real father.
Dad?